thatshow.com 2017-11-16

# Privacy Policy - Thatshow.com

## Privacy Policy

**Updated: March 1, 2015**

### Why we collect your information

Some of the features and services on thatshow.com require you to create an account and become a member. When signing up to be a member we collect personal information that can identify you. Personal information may include your name, email address, a password and other information that does not identify you. When you provide personal information through our website, this information may be sent to servers located in the United States and other countries around the world.

We do **NOT** sell or share any of your data with others without your prior consent. Your email is only used to identify you or contact you with important information about your thatshow.com account.

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or our Terms & Conditions please Contact Us.

### Acceptance

You must be at least 18 years of age or older to use the website and services of thatshow.com. When registering with thatshow.com to become a member you must provide true and accurate information and agree to our Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions.

**By using thatshow.com or any of our services, you are accepting the terms of our Privacy Policy and Terms & Conditions.**

### Cookies & Tracking

Currently, thatshow.com does not collect personal information or use cookies, advertisements or any other means to track browsing or viewing habits of its members. Please keep in mind that members of thatshow.com post videos, comments or other media which may contain links to third party websites that do not operate under our Privacy Policy and Terms & Conditions. 

### Information you share

Some of the services at thatshow.com let you share information with others. Please remember that when you share information publicly, it may be indexable by search engines. Our services provide you with different options on sharing and removing your content.

### Changes to our Practices or Policies

We will occasionally update our Privacy Policy and Terms & Conditions to reflect changes in our practices and services. When any changes are made to these documents we will revise the "Last Updated" date at the top of both documents. If we make any material changes in the way we collect, use, and/or share your personal information, we will notify you by sending an email to the most recent email address provided to us in your account, profile or registration (unless we do not have such an email address), and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on our website. We recommend that you check both the Privacy Policy and Terms & Conditions on our website from time to time to inform yourself of any changes in these or other policies.

### Terms & Conditions

Please review our  Terms & Conditions agreement, which forms a part of our Privacy Policy agreement.

### Indemnification

You will indemnify, defend, and hold harmless thatshow.com and its affiliates, directors, officers, employees, and agents, from and against all third party actions that: (1) arise from your activities on the thatshow.com website; (2) show a violation by you of any term of this Agreement; (3) asserts any content you submitted to thatshow.com violates any law or infringes on any third party right, including any intellectual property or privacy right.

### Copyrights and Other Rights

Thatshow.com respects the intellectual property rights of others. If you believe that your copyright or other intellectual property rights have been infringed upon by one of our members, please Contact Us in writing.

### Links

As a convenience to our users and members, thatshow.com may contain links to websites owned and operated by other entities. If you decide to visit any website linked to thatshow.com, you do so at your own risk and it is your responsibility to take all protective measures to guard against viruses or other destructive elements. Thatshow.com has no responsibility to you with respect to any website linked to thatshow.com, regardless of the linking form (e.g. advertising, pop-ups, hypertext links, image links) is maintained, controlled, endorsed, monitored or otherwise governed by thatshow.com.  

**MODIFICATION:** This Agreement may not be modified in any way except by a revised Privacy Policy Agreement posted by thatshow.com. A revised Privacy Policy will be effective as of the date it is posted on the thatshow.com website.

**ENTIRE AGREEMENT:** This Agreement also includes the thatshow.com Terms & Conditions.

This Agreement constitutes the entire understanding between thatshow.com and you concerning the subject matter hereof and supersedes all prior agreements and understandings regarding the same.
